# AYUSH KUMAR

(+91) 85278 85303 · aayushkumar12228@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/ayush-kumar-32856025a https://github.com/lachimolala2628 New Delhi, India

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

An experienced web developer with knowledge of advanced development phases such as testing, debugging, and user interface design. knowledgeable about every aspect of the web system lifecycle, including design, implementation, testing, and maintenance. possesses a broad skill set and is proficient in many different technologies. able to work well in cooperative team settings and independently manage projects.

| SKILLS                 |                         |                           |
|------------------------|-------------------------|---------------------------|
| HTML & CSS { Expert }  | JavaScript { SkillFul } | WordPress { Experienced } |
| TailWindCSS { Expert } | ReactJS { SkillFul }    | Shopify { Experienced }   |
| BootStrap 5 { Expert } | GSAP { SkillFul }       | WIX { Experienced }       |
| Media Query { Expert } | SEO { SkillFul }        | WebFlow { Experienced }   |
| Sass/Scss { SkillFul } | GitHub { SkillFul }     | Elementor { Experienced } |

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### • Timeless Unisex Salon

Oct, 2023 - Dec, 2023

Description: Designed and developed the company website to improve its user experience and increase conversions.

**Role: Web Developer** 

Contributions: Developed the new website using HTML, CSS, ReactJS, Bootstrap 5 and JavaScript. I created a visually appealing user-friendly, mobile-friendly and easier-to-navigate layout. Optimized the website for search engines.

#### · Oraanj-Interior Design

May, 2023 - Jul, 2023

Description: Redesigned and developed the company website to improve its user experience and increase conversions.

# **Role: Web Developer**

Contributions: Developed the new website using PHP, HTML, CSS, BootStrap 5, and JavaScript. I created a visually appealing user-friendly, mobile-friendly and easier-to-navigate layout. Optimized the website for search engines.

• Holyherbs Mar, 2024 - Apr, 2024

Description: Redesigned and payment-integrated the company website to improve its user experience and increase conversions.

# **Role: Web Developer**

Contributions: Developed the new website using WordPress and Elementor. I created a visually appealing user-friendly, mobile-friendly and easier-to-navigate layout. Optimized the website for search engines.

#### · Apple iPhone Clone website

Description: Cloned and redesigned the company website to improve my skills.

**Role: Web Developer** 

Contributions: Developed the new website using ReactJS, Vite, TailwindCSS, ThreeJS, GSAP, and JavaScript. I created a visually appealing and user-friendly layout.

# Weather App

Description: Designed and developed the website to improve my skills.

**Role: Web Developer** 

Contributions: Developed the new website using ReactJS, Vite, TailWindCSS, and JavaScript. I created a visually appealing and user-friendly layout.

#### • E-commerce Website

Description: Designed and developed the website to improve my skills and its user experience. The new website is more mobile-friendly and easier to navigate.

**Role: Web Developer** 

Contributions: Developed the new website using ReactJS, Vite, TailWindCSS, JavaScript and FakeStore API I created a visually appealing and user-friendly layout.

### **EDUCATION**

University of Delhi (School of open learning)

Jan, 2023 - Present

**Bachelor of Arts** 

Vidya Bhawan Mahavidyalaya Senior Secondary School

Jul, 2020 - Jun, 2022

Graduate Certificate in High School (Arts Stream)

Vidya Bhawan Mahavidyalaya Senior Secondary School

May, 2018 - Jul, 2020

Graduate Certificate in Secondary School

#### COURSES

Dice Academy Oct, 2022 - Apr, 2023

Web Design

**Google Analytics Academy** 

Google Analytics for Beginners

# **LANGUAGES**

English
Cood Working Knowledge
Cood Working Knowledge

Good Working Knowledge Good Working Knowledge